export const QuizQuestions = [
    {
        question: "Which language runs in a web browser?",
        options:[ "Java", "C", "Python", "JavaScript"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "What is the correct command to create a new React project?",
        options:["npm create-react-app", "npm create-react-app myProject", "npx create-react-app", "npx create-react-app myProject"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "What is the default port number in which the application run?",
        options: ["3000", "8080", "4040", "2000"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is a way to handle data in React.js ?",
        options: ["Services & Components", "State & Services", "State & Props", "none of the above"],
        answer:3
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is must for the API in React.js?",
        options: ["SetinitialComponent", "renderComponent", "render", "All of the above"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What is the role of ProtoTypes in React?",
        options: ["To define state","To define HTML Tree","To define dataType of Props","To define dataType of variables"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What is the purpose of Key attribute?",
        options: ["For styling list","For changing list","For uniquely identifying list items","For creating a list"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What does Redux provide for managing the state?",
        options: ["Centralized state management","Remote state management","Store","Private state management"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What is the significance of react virtual dom?",
        options: ["Improving reconciliation","Replacement for DOM","Server side rendering","Replcement for Redux"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is true regarding Babel?",
        options: ["Transpilar", "Compiler", "Both of the Above", "None of the Above"],
        answer: 3
    }
];